Press Gang Printers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Printing samples, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6; 1.64 m of graphic material 32 photographs 13 printing plates; Physical description: 15 photographs located in F-134-6-2-0-29 Physical description: 2 photographs located in F-134-6-4-0-32 Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-134-6-4-0-110 Physical 
  - Publications, 1971 - 1992; F-134-6-4; 1.07 m of textual records 1.07 m of graphic material 17 photographs
    - Contact Women's Group Society (Williams Lake): Finding a Job is Hard Work, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-51 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Corrective Collective: If We Didn't Laugh We'd Cry, 1972; F-134-6-4-0-52 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - If We Didn't Laugh We'd Cry: Corrective Collective, 1972; F-134-6-4-0-52-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item170.
    - Counterplay Magazine, 1986; F-134-6-4-0-53 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Disabled Women's Network of British Columbia: Proceedings, 1986; F-134-6-4-0-54 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Diversity: The Lesbian Rag, 1988; F-134-6-4-0-55 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Domestic Workers Union: The Domestic Worker (newsletter), 1982; F-134-6-4-0-56 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Downtown East (newspaper), 1974; F-134-6-4-0-57 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Downtown East, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-57-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item171.
      - Downtown East, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-57-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item172.
      - Downtown East, vol. 1 no. 5, August 1974; F-134-6-4-0-57-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item173.
    - Downtown Eastside Residents Association, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-58 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Downtown Eastside Women's Centre, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-59 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Earthwalk Guidebook, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-60 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Emily Carr College of Art: X - The Student Newspaper, vol. 1, 1978 - 1980; F-134-6-4-0-61 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - The Vancouver X: Emily Carr College of Art, vol. 1 no. 10, February 1979; F-134-6-4-0-61-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item174.
    - Emily Carr College of Art: X - The Student Newspaper, vol. 2, 1978 - 1980; F-134-6-4-0-62
    - Fed-up Newsletter, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-63 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Fed-up Newsletter, August 1974; F-134-6-4-0-63-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item175.
      - Fed-up Newsletter, September 1974; F-134-6-4-0-63-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item176.
    - Fissure Publications, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-64 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Free Childbirth Education Centre: Free Delivery, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-65 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Free the Five Defence Group, 1983 - 1985; F-134-6-4-0-66 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Frontline Advocacy Workers: FLAWline Newsletter, 1988 - 1989; F-134-6-4-0-67 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Gay Tide, 1973 - 1974; F-134-6-4-0-68 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Gay Tide, vol. 1 no. 1, August 1973; F-134-6-4-0-68-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item177.
      - Gay Tide, vol. 1 no. 1, August 1973; F-134-6-4-0-68-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item178.
      - Gay Tide, vol. 1 no. 2, October 1973; F-134-6-4-0-68-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item179.
      - Gay Tide, vol. 1 no. 2, October 1973; F-134-6-4-0-68-4 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item180.
      - Gay Tide, vol. 1 no. 3, November 1973; F-134-6-4-0-68-5 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item181.
      - Gay Tide, vol. 1 no. 3, November 1973; F-134-6-4-0-68-6 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item182.
      - Gay Tide, vol. 1 no. 4, January 1974; F-134-6-4-0-68-7 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item183.
      - Gay Tide, vol. 1 no. 4, January 1974; F-134-6-4-0-68-8 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item184.
      - Gay Tide no. 19, April 1978; F-134-6-4-0-68-9 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item185.
      - Gay Tide no. 23, December 1979; F-134-6-4-0-68-10 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item186.
      - Gay Tide no. 24, February 1980; F-134-6-4-0-68-11 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item187.
    - Greater Vancouver Business Association: Directory, 1985; F-134-6-4-0-69 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Greater Vancouver Foodbank: The Bottom Line (newsletter), 1988; F-134-6-4-0-70 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Greenpeace, 1990; F-134-6-4-0-71 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
      Print copy of a Greenpeace information sheet entitled "Dioxins, Furans and PCBs: The True Story".
    - Greenthumb Theatre for Young People, 1989 - 1990; F-134-6-4-0-72 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Growing Pains: A Newsletter About Children, 1974 - 1975; F-134-6-4-0-73 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Ragamuffin: A Newsletter About Childcare, vol. 1 no. 1, October 1974; F-134-6-4-0-73-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item188.
      - Growing Pains: A Newsletter About Childcare, vol. 1 no. 2, December 1974; F-134-6-4-0-73-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item189.
      - Growing Pains: A Newsletter About Childcare, vol. 1 no. 5, July 1975; F-134-6-4-0-73-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item190.
      - Growing Pains: A Newsletter About Childcare, vol. 1 no. 5, July 1975; F-134-6-4-0-73-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item191.
    - Hags Rag (magazine), 1984; F-134-6-4-0-74 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Hatching: An Illustrated Women's Liberation Diary, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-75 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Hatching: An Illustrated Women's Liberation Diary, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-75-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item192.
      - Hatching: An Illustrated Women's Liberation Diary, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-75-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item193.
      - Hatching: An Illustrated Women's Liberation Diary, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-75-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item194.
      - Hatching: An Illustrated Women's Liberation Diary, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-75-4 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item195.
    - Health Care Advocates at the B.C. Royal Commission on Health Care and Costs: Pulse (newsletter), 1990 - 1991; F-134-6-4-0-76 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Horizon Distributors: Buying Club Catalogue, 1990; F-134-6-4-0-77 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Housewives in Training and Research, 1986 - 1987; F-134-6-4-0-78 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Industrial Workers of the World, 1972 - 1989; F-134-6-4-0-79 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - International Committee Against Racism: INCAR News, 1981 - 1982; F-134-6-4-0-80 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - International Gay and Lesbian Acquatics Championships, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-81 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - International Women's Day, 1977; F-134-6-4-0-82 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - International Women's Day, March 1977; F-134-6-4-0-82-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item196.
    - Island Talk, 1983; F-134-6-4-0-83 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Jews Against Zionism, 1982; F-134-6-4-0-84 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Justice Institute of British Columbia, 1987 - 1989; F-134-6-4-0-85 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Kootenay Women's Council: Images, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-86 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Images: Kootenay Women's Council, February 1975; F-134-6-4-0-86-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item197.
    - Kriana: Freedom from Menstrual Pain, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-87 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Kwantlen College Women's Centre: Kwantlen Women's Handbook, 1983; F-134-6-4-0-88 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Labour Advocacy and Research Association, 1979; F-134-6-4-0-89 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Lam, Faith: Citizenship Class Notes, 1977; F-134-6-4-0-90 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Legal Services Commission, 1976 - 1983; F-134-6-4-0-91 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Legal Services Commission: Public Schools Legal Education Project Newsletter, 1976 - 1977; F-134-6-4-0-92
    - Lesbian Conference, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-93 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Maternal Health Society: Midwifery is a Labour of Love, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-94 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Mental Patients Association, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-95 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - Mental Patients Association: In a Nutshell, 1973 - 1977; F-134-6-4-0-96 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 1, February 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item198.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 2, March 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item199.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 2, March 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item200.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 3, May 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-4 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item201.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 4, June 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-5 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item202.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 4, June 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-6 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item203.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 5, August 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-7 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item204.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 5, August 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-8 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item205.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 6, September 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-9 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item206.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 2 no. 6, September 1973; F-134-6-4-0-96-10 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item207.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 3 no. 8, May 1975; F-134-6-4-0-96-11 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item208.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 5 no. 3, July 1977; F-134-6-4-0-96-12 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item209.
      - In A Nutshell: Mental Patients Association Newsletter, vol. 5 no. 3, July 1977; F-134-6-4-0-96-13 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item210.
    - Midwifery Task Force Journal, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-97 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - National Resource Centre on Political Prisoners and Anti-Martial Law Coalition: Tanod, 1980; F-134-6-4-0-98 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - New Democratic Party (BC) Women's Committee: Priority (magazine), vol. 1, 1975 - 1979; F-134-6-4-0-99 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - New Democratic Party (BC) Women's Committee: Priority (magazine), vol. 2, 1975 - 1979; F-134-6-4-0-100 (Archival box - standard 134-23)
    - New Democratic Party (BC) Women's Committee: Priority (magazine), vol. 3, 1975 - 1979; F-134-6-4-0-101 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - New Democratic Party (BC) Women's Committee: publications, 1977; F-134-6-4-0-102 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Outlet, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-103 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Outlet, vol. 1 no. 10, May 1974; F-134-6-4-0-103-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item211.
      - Outlet, vol. 1 no. 16, July 1974; F-134-6-4-0-103-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item212.
      - Outlet, vol. 1 no. 17, July 1974; F-134-6-4-0-103-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item213.
      - Outlet, vol. 1 no. 18, August 1974; F-134-6-4-0-103-4 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item214.
      - Outlet, vol. 1 no. 18, August 1974; F-134-6-4-0-103-5 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item215.
    - Oxfam, 1989 - 1990; F-134-6-4-0-104 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Pacific Post Partum Support Society: Post Partum Depression and Anxiety, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-105 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Pacific Reforestration Workers Association, 1982 - 1987; F-134-6-4-0-106 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Pan-Canadian Conference on Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1992; F-134-6-4-0-107 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Peak, 1974 - 1975; F-134-6-4-0-108 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - The Peak, vol. 39 no. 10, March 1974; F-134-6-4-0-108-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item216.
      - The Peak, May 1975; F-134-6-4-0-108-2 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item217.
    - Pedestal, 1972 - 1975; F-134-6-4-0-109 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Pedestal, vol. 4 no. 7, August 1972; F-134-6-4-0-109-1 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item250.
      - Pedestal, vol. 4 no. 9, November 1972; F-134-6-4-0-109-2 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item251.
      - Pedestal, vol. 5 no. 1, January 1973; F-134-6-4-0-109-3 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item252.
      - Pedestal, vol. 5 no. 3, March 1973; F-134-6-4-0-109-4 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item253.
      - Pedestal, vol. 5 no. 4, April 1973; F-134-6-4-0-109-5 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item254.
      - Pedestal, vol. 5 no. 5, June 1973; F-134-6-4-0-109-6 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item255.
      - Pedestal, vol. 5 no. 5, June 1973; F-134-6-4-0-109-7 (Newspaper box 134-36)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item256.
      - Pedestal, vol. 5 no. 6, October 1973; F-134-6-4-0-109-8 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item257.
      - Pedestal, vol. 6 no. 1, January 1974; F-134-6-4-0-109-9 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item258.
      - Women Can. (formerly the Pedestal), vol. 6 no. 4, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-109-10 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item259.
      - Pedestal, vol. 7 no. 3, October 1975; F-134-6-4-0-109-11 (Newspaper box 134-35)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item260.
    - Pedestal - Photographs, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-110 (Archival box - small 134-33)
    - People's Self Help Centre, 1976; F-134-6-4-0-111 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - The People's Self-Help Centre, April 1976; F-134-6-4-0-111-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item218.
    - Philippine National Day, 1981 - 1982; F-134-6-4-0-112 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Planned Parenthood Association of British Columbia: Human Sexuality: An Annotated Bibliography of Educational Resources, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-113 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Port Coquitlam Area Women's Centre: Policies and Procedures Manual, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-114 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Press Gang Publishers, 1981 - 1989; F-134-6-4-0-115 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Public Service Alliance of Canada: Pacific Digest, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-116 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Randall, Nora D.: Sounds Like a Carnaval, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-117 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Ray-Cam Cooperative Centre: Spring Program, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-118 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Returning (booklet), 1972; F-134-6-4-0-119 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - S.C.U.M.: Woman to Woman (book), [197-?]; F-134-6-4-0-120 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Satellite Video Exchange Society: directories, 1977 - 1978; F-134-6-4-0-121 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - School Peacemakers Education Project: Peer Conflict Resolution Through Creative Negotiation, 1987; F-134-6-4-0-122 (Archival box - standard 134-24)
    - Scott, Jack: Martyrs and Militia, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-123 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - Martyrs and Militia, June 1973; F-134-6-4-0-123-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item219.
    - Scott, Jack: Martyrs and Militia - photographs, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-124 (Archival box - small 134-33)
    - Service, Office, and Retail Workers Union of Canada, 1977 - 1986; F-134-6-4-0-125 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Service, Office, and Retail Workers Union of Canada: SORWUC News, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-126 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - SORWUC News, vol. 1 no. 1, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-126-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item220.
      - SORWUC News, vol. 1 no. 1, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-126-2 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item221.
    - SFU Week, 1977; F-134-6-4-0-127 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Socialist Challenge, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-128 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Solidarity Committee with the People of Guatemala: Guatemala Vencera, 1981 - 1984; F-134-6-4-0-129 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Song Sheet: International Women's Day, 1979; F-134-6-4-0-130 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Strathcona News, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-131 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - Strathcona News, June 1975; F-134-6-4-0-131-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item222.
    - Talking Drum: Downtown Eastside Cultural Sharing Newsletter, 1990; F-134-6-4-0-132 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Teachers' Committee on El Salvador: Agenda Book, 1988; F-134-6-4-0-133 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Teaching Support Staff Union (TSSU): Bulletin, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-134 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - The News, 1973 - 1974; F-134-6-4-0-135 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - The News, vol. 1, December 1973; F-134-6-4-0-135-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item223.
      - The News, vol. 2, January 1974; F-134-6-4-0-135-2 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item224.
    - Titmouse Review, 1972; F-134-6-4-0-136 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Tools for Peace: Resource Kit Update, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-137 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - United Housing Foundation: From the Ground, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-138 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - United Nations Association in Canada - Vancouver Branch: International Human Rights Day Information Kit, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-139 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - University Arts Association of Canada - Women's Caucus: Newsletter, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-140 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - University of British Columbia Anarchist Club, 1983; F-134-6-4-0-141 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - University of British Columbia Women's Centre: UBC Women's Handbook, 1978; F-134-6-4-0-142 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - University of British Columbia Women's Studies: Women Poets Read, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-143 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver and District Public Housing Tenants Association Newsletter, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-144 (Newspaper box 134-32)
    - Vancouver and District Public Housing Tenants Association Newsletter - photographs, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-145 (Archival box - small 134-33)
      - Citizens United: The Vancouver and District Public Housing Tenants Association Newsletter, June 1973; F-134-6-4-0-145-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item225.
    - Vancouver Chilean Society, 1975 - 1979; F-134-6-4-0-146 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver Co-op Radio, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-147 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - Vancouver Co-operative Radio CFRO 102.7 FM, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-147-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item226.
    - Vancouver Co-op Radio: The Volunteers' Newsletter, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-148 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver East Housing Co-op: Scatterchatter (newsletter), February 1986; F-134-6-4-0-149 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver Outdoor Club for Women, 1988; F-134-6-4-0-150 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver Radical Therapy Collective, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-151 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver Rape Relief, 1979 - 1986; F-134-6-4-0-152 (Archival box - standard 134-25)
    - Vancouver Status of Women Newsletter, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-153 (Newspaper box 134-32)
      - Vancouver Status of Women Newsletter, vol. 3 no. 25, September 1973; F-134-6-4-0-153-1 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item227.
      - Vancouver Status of Women Newsletter, vol. 3 no. 26, October 1973; F-134-6-4-0-153-2 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item228.
      - Vancouver Status of Women Newsletter, vol. 3 no. 26, October 1973; F-134-6-4-0-153-3 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item229.
      - Vancouver Status of Women Newsletter, vol. 3 no. 27, November 1973; F-134-6-4-0-153-4 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item230.
      - Vancouver Status of Women Newsletter, vol. 3 no. 28, December 1973; F-134-6-4-0-153-5 (Newspaper box 134-32)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item231.